<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Open Monster Vision</title>
    <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Open Monster Vision</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 04:53:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning the D and D Monster Manual into JSON</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/turning-dungeons-and-dragons-monster-manual-pdf-into-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 04:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/turning-dungeons-and-dragons-monster-manual-pdf-into-json/</guid>
      <description>The What I found a PDF copy of the monster manual (Of course I also own a copy, but I needed digital for this). I was able to grep out all the tables for monster stats&amp;hellip;however, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a way to programatically get their names so I assigned them ID numbers. Git Repo
GNU vs BSD Tools Though generally I script on my mac, I use the gnu tools vs the bsd tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP Recruiting Email</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/php-recruiting-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 08:04:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/php-recruiting-email/</guid>
      <description>An email from a recruiter Dustin,
Always Are you ready to take the next steps in your career? &amp;lt; YES
But No one wants to do php I’ve got a client looking for a PHP Developer (Laravel, Javascript) in Nashville, TN. The full job description is below. &amp;lt; So steps backwards?
Indeed If you are a PHP Developer with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing &amp;lt; I am and this makes me sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grubby Little Hacker</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/grubby-little-hacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 02:12:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/grubby-little-hacker/</guid>
      <description>All I have ever wanted and strived to be is, a grubby little hacker. Those three words written indelibly in my mind:
grubby little hacker
Always lower case. In fiction they were smart, they were generally physically weaker than their antagonists, but clever won the day. I became enamored with the idea after the advent of getting my first computer, an IBM PS/1 486 25 Mhz, Both types of floppy drives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Data IRL Maps</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/data-irl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 17:45:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/data-irl/</guid>
      <description>I used to live in Philadelphia 
I assure I commited neither. I got the dataset here.
The Code library(&amp;quot;ggplot2&amp;quot;) library(&amp;quot;ggmap&amp;quot;) #Get Philadelphia Crime Data, this takes a while philCrimeData &amp;lt;- read.csv(&amp;quot;~/Downloads/crime.csv&amp;quot;,stringsAsFactors = FALSE) # Get Philly Map, Zoom in slightly philCrimeMap &amp;lt;- get_map(location = &amp;quot;philadelphia&amp;quot;,maptype = &amp;quot;roadmap&amp;quot;, zoom = 12) #Create Map philCrimeMapGG &amp;lt;- ggmap(philCrimeMap) #Create My Address me &amp;lt;- data.frame( Lon = c(-75.112021), Lat = c(39.991058), Crime = &amp;quot;Me&amp;quot;, stringsAsFactors = FALSE ) #Data Needs to be arranged so that the legend prints properly #Create rapes table rapes &amp;lt;- philCrimeData[which( philCrimeData$Text_General_Code == &#39;Rape&#39; ),] rapes &amp;lt;- rapes[,c(&amp;quot;Lat&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;Lon&amp;quot;)] #Create Crime Col rapes$Crime &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;Rapes&amp;quot; #Create Murders Table murders &amp;lt;- philCrimeData[grep(pattern = &amp;quot;Homicide&amp;quot;,philCrimeData$Text_General_Code),] murders &amp;lt;- murders[,c(&amp;quot;Lat&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;Lon&amp;quot;)] #Create Crime Col murders$Crime &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;Homicides&amp;quot; #Bind Tables Crimes &amp;lt;- rbind(rapes, murders) #Add Dots pngf &amp;lt;- philCrimeMapGG + #Make Crime dots, There&#39;s a lot So make them Transparent geom_point(show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not to Turn 10000 Json Files Into One Database, The Perils of Freelancing</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-turn-1000-json-files-into-one-csv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 14:37:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-turn-1000-json-files-into-one-csv/</guid>
      <description>The Wrong Way Worse Is Better As a grubby unix hacker, I usually take the easy way on my projects. And as of late, I have been getting fairly simple data conversion jobs from various freelancing sites and customers. So of course, worse is better is my go to philosophy. Well this dug &amp;lsquo;ol @bsdpunk into a little hole. I got a couple of example JSON files, from a guy who said he had a lot of data and wanted to turn them into a single CSV, to load into BigQuery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Werner Hertzog Destroyed Me at Linux Fu - Best Job Interview Ever</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/werner-hertzog-destroyed-me-at-linux-fu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 23:14:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/werner-hertzog-destroyed-me-at-linux-fu/</guid>
      <description>The Who I am @bsdpunk and I think I am good at things, particularly interviews and linux. I fancy myself a pretty good interviewer. I&amp;rsquo;m a goofball&amp;hellip;like cringe worthy goofy. I usually use this to my advantage in an interview. I do my goofy laugh, at the start and when I get something wrong, I say some weird dad joke or something, and then I&amp;rsquo;m determined non-threatening, which I am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Have an Honest Conversation About Recruiters</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/lets-have-an-honest-conversation-about-recruiters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 11:14:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/lets-have-an-honest-conversation-about-recruiters/</guid>
      <description>The What I lied, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a goddamned conversation, there&amp;rsquo;s no commenting on this blog. You&amp;rsquo;re going to listen to why the title recruiter is another way of saying &amp;ldquo;demon from the really lame Dante&amp;rsquo;s Inferno level, where you waste time for all eternity&amp;rdquo;. There are exceptions of course, see the section entitled The Exceptions.
The Why I have been hurt by recruiters, but that&amp;rsquo;s not what makes them such a wonderful target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Neural Net to Predict Tom Brady&#39;s Fantasy Points</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/building-a-neural-net-to-predict-tom-bradys-fantasy-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 08:04:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/building-a-neural-net-to-predict-tom-bradys-fantasy-points/</guid>
      <description>The Who I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to tie my shoes, this will come into play later.
The Why So we can all make lots of money gambling. Wait, is it even gambling then? Oh no, it isn&amp;rsquo;t remember DraftKings is legal because it&amp;rsquo;s a game of skill. The Code Let&amp;rsquo;s Build this thing. I used R, you can use whatever plebian language you prefer. #Import Tom Brady Data tombrady &amp;lt;- read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money Using Grep Sed and Awk</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-to-make-money-using-grep-sed-and-awk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 04:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-to-make-money-using-grep-sed-and-awk/</guid>
      <description>The Who I&amp;rsquo;m your friendly neighborhood unix man. And I have a problem. I love regex. Now I have two problems.
The Why Recently I have become destitute so I have taken to using the skills I have to provide for my poor sick family. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly disabled cats. And when all you have is hammer, everything gets nailed. So I thought, you know what people probably don&amp;rsquo;t automate enough of&amp;hellip;Data Entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not to Get a Job With an Elite Tech Company</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-get-a-job-with-an-elite-tech-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 11:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-get-a-job-with-an-elite-tech-company/</guid>
      <description>I am an Expert Let&amp;rsquo;s establish the parameters of what makes me an expert on not getting an elite job with a tech company. I have interviewed for an SRE(Site Reliability Engineer) role, at both Google and facebook, and failed to achieve those positions. Last month I interviewed for an SRE for one of the top 25 most visited sites, and also failed to achieve that position. Why on September 13th I didn&amp;rsquo;t even bother to respond to this Vimeo voice mail I am the Michael Jordan, of not achieving an engineering position with elite Silicon Valley tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>