<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sed on Open Monster Vision</title>
    <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/tags/sed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sed on Open Monster Vision</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 04:53:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/tags/sed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning the D and D Monster Manual into JSON</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/turning-dungeons-and-dragons-monster-manual-pdf-into-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 04:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/turning-dungeons-and-dragons-monster-manual-pdf-into-json/</guid>
      <description>The What I found a PDF copy of the monster manual (Of course I also own a copy, but I needed digital for this). I was able to grep out all the tables for monster stats&amp;hellip;however, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a way to programatically get their names so I assigned them ID numbers. Git Repo
GNU vs BSD Tools Though generally I script on my mac, I use the gnu tools vs the bsd tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not to Turn 10000 Json Files Into One Database, The Perils of Freelancing</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-turn-1000-json-files-into-one-csv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 14:37:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-turn-1000-json-files-into-one-csv/</guid>
      <description>The Wrong Way Worse Is Better As a grubby unix hacker, I usually take the easy way on my projects. And as of late, I have been getting fairly simple data conversion jobs from various freelancing sites and customers. So of course, worse is better is my go to philosophy. Well this dug &amp;lsquo;ol @bsdpunk into a little hole. I got a couple of example JSON files, from a guy who said he had a lot of data and wanted to turn them into a single CSV, to load into BigQuery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money Using Grep Sed and Awk</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-to-make-money-using-grep-sed-and-awk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 04:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-to-make-money-using-grep-sed-and-awk/</guid>
      <description>The Who I&amp;rsquo;m your friendly neighborhood unix man. And I have a problem. I love regex. Now I have two problems.
The Why Recently I have become destitute so I have taken to using the skills I have to provide for my poor sick family. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly disabled cats. And when all you have is hammer, everything gets nailed. So I thought, you know what people probably don&amp;rsquo;t automate enough of&amp;hellip;Data Entry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>