<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Open Monster Vision</title>
    <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Open Monster Vision</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 14:15:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>That Time I Worked for A Criminal Organization</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/that-time-i-worked-for-criminals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 14:15:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/that-time-i-worked-for-criminals/</guid>
      <description>That time I was employed by a criminal organization I was employed by Micfo for several months, I quickly determined that they were shady and invovled in illegal practices. I did not quit because of that, I quit because I felt unwanted, by HR and Management. Later they would ask me to come back. This is the full story. There will be amazon affiliate links at the end of the page in the epiloge(I am currently unemployed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not to Build a Cli With Node</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-build-a-cli-with-node/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 17:21:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-build-a-cli-with-node/</guid>
      <description>The Who I&amp;rsquo;m just a dude, that writes shit down. Occasionally I write something useful for sys admins, but mostly my github is a garbage place where ideas go to die. I am @bsdpunk, and I am a terrible person. And mostly I write shells that don&amp;rsquo;t currently work, but maybe did at one time, or maybe can if you give me a minute.
The What This guy wrote a post I don&amp;rsquo;t agree with and I&amp;rsquo;m going to complain about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning the D and D Monster Manual into JSON</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/turning-dungeons-and-dragons-monster-manual-pdf-into-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 04:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/turning-dungeons-and-dragons-monster-manual-pdf-into-json/</guid>
      <description>The What I found a PDF copy of the monster manual (Of course I also own a copy, but I needed digital for this). I was able to grep out all the tables for monster stats&amp;hellip;however, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find a way to programatically get their names so I assigned them ID numbers. Git Repo
GNU vs BSD Tools Though generally I script on my mac, I use the gnu tools vs the bsd tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money Using Grep Sed and Awk</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-to-make-money-using-grep-sed-and-awk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 04:53:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-to-make-money-using-grep-sed-and-awk/</guid>
      <description>The Who I&amp;rsquo;m your friendly neighborhood unix man. And I have a problem. I love regex. Now I have two problems.
The Why Recently I have become destitute so I have taken to using the skills I have to provide for my poor sick family. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly disabled cats. And when all you have is hammer, everything gets nailed. So I thought, you know what people probably don&amp;rsquo;t automate enough of&amp;hellip;Data Entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Not to Get a Job With an Elite Tech Company</title>
      <link>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-get-a-job-with-an-elite-tech-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 11:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openmonstervision.github.io/blog/posts/how-not-to-get-a-job-with-an-elite-tech-company/</guid>
      <description>I am an Expert Let&amp;rsquo;s establish the parameters of what makes me an expert on not getting an elite job with a tech company. I have interviewed for an SRE(Site Reliability Engineer) role, at both Google and facebook, and failed to achieve those positions. Last month I interviewed for an SRE for one of the top 25 most visited sites, and also failed to achieve that position. Why on September 13th I didn&amp;rsquo;t even bother to respond to this Vimeo voice mail I am the Michael Jordan, of not achieving an engineering position with elite Silicon Valley tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>